# Summary\_

I am a Computer Systems engineering student in my final year at the University of Auckland. In addition to the postgraduate courses I'm currently taking, I tutor Stage 3 and Stage 2 courses, so that I can assist students in the years below me to become better programmers and engineers. I first started programming when I was 14 and enjoy spending my extra time working on a selection of projects to improve my current skill-set. On top of that, I study Japanese in what time I have left, so that I can experience another culture and widen my view of the world. I also practice Gōjū-Ryū Karate to keep myself fit.

### Skills.

**Frameworks** CherryPy, .NET Core, React

Languages C, C++, Java, Javascript, Lua, Matlab, MIPS Assembly Language, MySQL, Postgres, Python, Visual Basic .NET, VHDL

Operating Systems Linux, Windows, MacOS

**Software** Docker, Git, Grafana, Vim

## **Education**

#### **University of Auckland**

Auckland CBD, Auckland 1010

B.Eng (Hons) in Computer Systems

Mar 2017 - Nov 2020

Undergraduate degree combining Electrical Engineering and Software Engineering to create a holistic view of computers and their operations.

ACG Parnell College

Parnell, Auckland 1052

CAMBRIDGE INTERNATIONAL EXAMINATIONS

Jan 2012 - Dec 2016

Top-achieving student in A-Level Mathematics, Physics, Computer Science and AS English.

# **Experience**

**Teknique Ltd.**Rosedale, Auckland 0632

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

Nov 2019 - Feb 2020

- Developed visualisations using Grafana for use in a factory setting with a MySQL backend
- Worked on migrating a quality assurance test suite from Python2 to Python3
- Developed software tests for embedded camera solutions

#### **University of Auckland**

Auckland CBD, Auckland 1010

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

IT TECHNICIAN

Nov 2018 - Feb 2019

- · Worked with a PhD candidate on an evaluation script for automated workflows of a person tracking algorithm using the OpenCV library
- Developed a Python script to generate metrics for precise and consistent evaluation

University of Auckland CBD, Auckland 1010

TEACHING ASSISTANT

July 2019 - Present

- Assisted students in learning the fundamentals of Object Oriented Programming in C++
- Marked assignments, held lab sessions, invigilated tests, etc.

#### **Epsom Girls Grammar School**

Epsom, Auckland 1023 Nov 2017 - Dec 2017, Jun 2018

• Assisted the IT department in server maintenance

• Provided IT support to a student body in excess of 2000 students

#### **Epsom Girls Grammar School**

Epsom, Auckland 1023

DIGITAL EXAMINATIONS CO-COORDINATOR

Nov 2017, Nov 2018, Nov 2019

- · Organised and managed the delivery of a digital platform for NCEA exams, in participation with NZQA, to over 300 students
- Invigilated over 40 exams from NCEA Level 1 through to NCEA Level 3

# Extracurricular Activity \_\_\_\_\_

#### Japanese Auckland Meetup (JAM+)

Auckland, NZ

Jan 2018 - Present

• Managed the internal operations and online storage

- Managed the internal operations and online storage
- Organised merchandising (membership cards, etc.)
- Recorded items and outcomes of meetings

SECRETARY